Hello Hello,
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте
18 years old, you are 18 years old, you are 20, you
18 лет есть что вам 18 лет есть 20 есть
just look very young. Maybe it’s some
просто очень молодо выглядит Может это
kind of schoolgirl.
школьница какая-то Я из Украины город
give it to Germany
Как вы считаете нужно отдать Германии
Well, why look when Crimea was
Ну почему смотрите когда Крым был
Russian Yes it was Well yes Well
российский Да был
here
Ну да Ну тут
Not if but when, that is, when
Не если а когда то есть получается когда
I realized why the repeater is
понял почему репитер это
not look no No it was Swedish and
не смотри не Нет он был шведским да
then when Peter, as a result of the Northern
потом когда Петр в результате Северной
War, won back a piece there, he was
войны там отвоевал кусочек он там на
Swedish there  the fortress before he built the city, he
шведские крепости до построил город он
will depart like
отойдет типа
Independent Ingre will be to Ingermanland
Независимый ингре будет к ингерманландия
mystical region
мистерический регион
Well, how will she win You saw
Ну а что как она выиграет Вы же видели
what to do you are already starting to
что же делать вы уже начинаете в
fight in the middle of Russia there it is shooting down
середине России воевать там это сбивают
planes you have helicopters Prigozhin
самолеты у вас вертолеты Пригожин
together it doesn’t happen
вместе так не бывает
against the background of defeat
на фоне поражения
and who  said that I’m brave Well, at
а кто сказал что я смелая Ну вы по
least you’re not afraid, you’re not hiding and you’re not
крайней не боитесь не прячетесь и не
afraid to admit Yes, like, as a
боитесь признавать Да что типа в
result of a defeat, you’ll have to
результате поражения типа придется
leave for Moscow, but not everyone sounds like it Well,
уехать в Москву но не каждый это звучит
what kind of logical end will there be, but the
Ну а что какой логический конец будет но
logical end will come to us and
логический конец к нам придут и скажут
also say goodbye Leave
также досвидос Уезжай
that's all, well, what remains will do
все ну а что остается будет делать
nothing, and
ничего
you have some kind of car, there is a
а вас какая-то машина есть
car. What do you think, if you
автомобиль Как вы думаете вот если
look if when they come for
смотреть если когда Вот придут за
reparations, so you leave for
репарациями так вот вам уезжайте в
Moscow and I will take your property in order to
Москву а ваше имущество заберу для того
give it to Ukrainians as
чтобы украинцам отдать в качестве
reparations, what do you think?
репарации как думаете
I think if everyone just
Я не думаю если будут просто все отсюда
leaves here that someone will be there, I don’t know if he will
уезжать что кто-то будет там не знаю он
pick up the car, it will simply be
машину забрать это просто будет
impossible,
невозможно
that is, they will give these cars to Ukraine,
то есть эти машины отдадут в Украину
they will sell them
продадут
to fly away on what
улетать на чём
Well, how did they come, for example, to the Germans Let them
Ну а как пришли например немцам Дай
say Well, you are [ __ ] and that they were not
сказали Ну съёбываете и что им ничего не
given anything So  Kaliningrad, next to Germany,
дали Так Калининград рядом с Германией
once they crossed over, everyone will
раз перешли все
come to you, they will come Well, the Germans will
вам придут свои придут Ну немцы же будут
drive you out, they will bring Ukrainians
вас выгонять они приведут украинцев
Ukrainians living after this war will be
украинцы жилые после этой войны будут
you and Ukrainians You will have
вас и украинцы Вам будут
everything and you will have to very quickly Well,
и все и придется очень быстро
I don’t think that somehow very quickly
Ну я не думаю что как-то очень быстро
No it’s not  we’ll
Нет это не будет весь город
just give the whole city that
дадим просто что украинских солдат
I’ll bring Ukrainian soldiers so that they don’t take you there,
приведу чтобы не вас там выводили
for example,
например
it turns out only by sea, it will be necessary, that
получается только по морю надо будет то
is, you will sail some kind of barges
есть вы каких-то там баржах будете плыть
and, as I understand it, they
и так понимаю
say that Kaliningrad will be given away by the
утверждают что Калининград но отдадут
Ukrainians Well, what do you think Well, where are
украинцы Ну что вы думаете Ну а куда нам
you going to us  you ask Yes, how are we emigrating from here,
вот вы спрашиваете Да как мы отсюда
roughly speaking Well, how can I not say
грубо говоря Ну как не могу сказать На
Why I’ll come and shoot everyone Well, if you
что приду всех и перестреляют Ну если вы
don’t take weapons with him anymore to defend
с ним больше не возьмете оружие защищать
Kaliningrad is true
Калининград правда
Why think
Почему думать
defending Kaliningrad is
защищать Калининград
very well defended we have
очень хорошо защищается у нас проводится
exercises every day in our sky everything is
каждый день учения у нас в небе все
constantly  it flies if there is
постоянно летает это в случае если будет
someone to fly, look in Russia yes if
кому летать смотрите в России да если
Russia loses Why is it that
Россия проиграет Почему почему у меня
all my relatives are Ukrainians I’m a Ukrainian
все родственники [__] я [__] Вот
Khokhlushka That’s where
мало папа вот Кривой Рог Да смотри
you come from  You support
Значит тебя Ты кстати как относишься к
this war
этой войне Это поддерживаешь
How can I support what, well, what do
А как я могу поддерживать то что ну как
you think is right,
ты считаешь правильно
Russian [ __ ] Not well, ax
российский [__] Не ну топор
to me this cream to the [ __ ] Fenya, I’m there, why did
мне этот крем до ебени Фени я там ну что
they take Crimea? I’ll appear there at least once Well,
они Крым забрали Я там хоть раз появлюсь
what side will I be?
Ну а мне каким боком будет Ну как ты
it’s Ukraine or Russia,
считаешь что Крым это Украина или Россия
of course, because it’s
естественно Потому что это
not the one that is behind the scenes, keep quiet, yes,
не та которая там за кадром все молчи да
I tell everyone who is in the frame. In your
я говорю всем кто в кадр В вашем ваше
opinion, what a damn
мнение какое блин
kilogram of us is straight autumn at a time, and the experience is
нами килограмм прям за раз осень а опыт
driving us through quarries into a shadow ban
загоняя нас через карьерки в теневые бан
and even then the video is not shown  people are
и дуже то видео не показывается людям
often shown information about streams
часто показывается информация про стримы
in order to have an
для того
operational scroll
оперативный свиток
and we are with you
и мы с вами
[music]
[музыка]